amkingdom.com 2011-12-21

# AMKINGDOM Privacy Policy

**AMKINGDOM Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs your use and access to the following network of websites, which currently includes: (1) http://amkingdom.com; (2) http://AMKINGDOM.com; (3) http://amkingdom.com/hairy; (4) http://atkexotics.com; (5) http://atkarchives.com; (6) http://atkmovies.com; (7) http://www.atkpetites.com; (8) http://atklounge.com; and http://atkpremium.com (collectively, the "Sites" or individually, a "Site"). 

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Sites. By accessing and using our Sites, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Sites. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. The Sites request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and consult it regularly. 

**Protecting Your Files on Your Computer**

There are frequent instances where you may wish to maintain your privacy by keeping your Internet traces or sensitive files on your computer secure from others. We suggest that you consider privacy software such as PrivacyView.

PrivacyView protects all your sensitive and private files. This software encrypts Internet surfing traces and sensitive data. PrivacyView's system of secure password protection works much better than manually deleting Internet history, cookies, favorites and temp files.

In addition to privatizing the surfing experience, PrivacyView gives you the ability to conceal downloaded pictures and movies on your computer by encrypting and hiding the files. Once the downloaded content is stored, the images and movies can be searched and retrieved for viewing within PrivacyView.

The software is inexpensive, comes with support and instantly gives you piece of mind. You can learn more about privacy software, or try PrivacyView for free, at [www.privacyview.com](http://www.privacyview.com/affiliate_page.aspx?a_id=1083&c=246). 

**Information Collection and Use**

In certain areas of the Sites, we may request that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address,  birthdate, personal opinions, and personal preferences. We reserve the right to identify which informational items are mandatory and which are optional. We log all user's information when signing onto or using the Sites, including but not limited to IP address, URL of the Web page user was on before visiting the Sites, user's browser version, user's registration forms, surveys, cookie data, and communications transmitted through applications on the Sites.  We reserve the right to use this information to find ways to improve sales to a group of Site members, to increase the users experience according to their interests, or to formulate statistical models to accomplish the Sites' goals through surveys or contests. We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Sites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others without your express consent  . 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We will use cookies to track affiliate sales and referring URL's. In the future, we may use cookies to personalize services for members, to track browsers, to identify the most popular areas of our Sites, and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Sites (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Sharing**

We do not currently sell or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our products and services to benefit users, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership. 

**Law Enforcement**

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs. 

**Links**

These Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Sites they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Security**

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We use SSL encryption on all billing and membership transactions. We do not and will not in the future keep sensitive billing information on our local servers. The billing processors will keep this information. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures. 

**Children**

Our Sites are not intended for children under the age of 18 or 21, depending on the age of majority in your jurisdiction. Our Sites do not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes  or if a user no longer desires our services, you should contact us to correct or update your information. 

**Information Retention**

We retain all users' information in a secure database indefinitely. 

**Choice**

From time to time, we may send our users e-mail, e-mail newsletters, Site news updates, or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by choosing a "do not contact" option or by contacting us. We will comply with all requests for removal. 

**Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Sites. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use our Sites, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use our Sites after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice). 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can service you quicker. 

Please send your e-mail to: [support@amkingdom.com](mailto:support@amkingdom.com)

© Kingdom World Wide Web Operations, Inc. (2005)
